fitnessworld.com 2008-05-13

# Fitness Management Magazine - Issues & Solutions for Fitness Facilities

Fitness Management magazine respects the privacy of the users of its website, www.fitnessmanagement.com. We want to make your online experience as safe and satisfying as possible while visiting us on the Web.

Fitness Management will not collect information about you unless you choose to provide it to us.

## Information that Fitness Management Publications Tracks

  1. Fitness Management tallies page views and impressions throughout our site. This information allows us to better tailor our content to readers' needs and helps our advertisers understand the demographics of our audience. 
  2. Fitness Management tracks information that users provide through optional, voluntary submissions. These are voluntary submissions that are necessary to enter specific pages on the site that require registration. 

## Optional Voluntary Submission

We offer the following free services, which require some type of voluntary submission of personal information by users: 

  1. **Site Registration**  
To enter specific pages on the Fitness Management website, you will be asked to fill out an online registration form. This form asks for basic contact information and more specific information such as job title and affiliation with the industry. 

After initial registration, a "cookie" will be set in a user's browser. This enables the user to be "recognized" on future visits so that registration isn't required again. 

  2. **Subscription Request**  
If a user of our website wishes to request a subscription to the print copy of our magazine, a completed subscription form is reqeusted. If a current subscriber wishes to view his or her subscription information, a subscription number from the mailing label can be entered on the subscription form. All other fields on this form will then be pre-filled with contact information that the user can either submit or edit. 

The following pages on our website require site registration:

  1. **Featured Articles**  
Featured Articles (also know as "Premium Content") are select articles published from January 2005 to the present that are available only after registering for Premium Content on our site. 

The following pages on our website require voluntary submission of personal information: 

  1. **Job Postings**  
We invite users of our site to submit job opportunities to our online Classifieds. Users wishing to submit a job posting will be required to provide the job title, company, a brief description of the position and details on applying. The information will be posted on our site for up to 90 days. You may contact us to request removal of the ad at any time. 
  2. **Buyers Guide**  
We invite users of our site to search for industry suppliers and contact them through our online Buyers Guide form. Users wishing to submit a request via the Buyers Guide form will be required to provide name, company and email address. The information will be logged in a database as well as emailed to the selected suppliers. 
  3. **Readers Q &A**  
We invite users of our site to participate in the online forum, Readers Q&A. Users wishing to contribute to the Readers Q&A are not required to provide any personal data. The data submitted by users will be posted on our site for an undetermined amount of time. You may contact us to request removal of the submission at any time. 
  4. **Fitness Management Blog**  
We invite users of our site to participate in the FM Blog. Users wishing to contribute to the FM Blog are not required to provide any personal data. The data submitted by users will be posted on our site for an undetermined amount of time. You may contact us to request removal of the submissions at any time. W 

We reserve the right to reject any submission if we believe it to be false, libelous or if it contains profanity or is not related to the industry. We are not responsible if website users use the information presented on www.fitnessmanagement.com outside of its intended purpose. 

## Federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act

In accordance with the Federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without requesting parental consent. 

## Usage Tracking

Fitness Management Publications uses third-party software from Google Analytics to analyze user traffic patterns throughout our site. We do not correlate this information with data about individual users. With data supplied by Google Analytics, Fitness Management Publications breaks down overall usage statistics according to a user's domain name, browser type and MIME type by reading this information from the browser string (information contained in every user's browser). We do not track what individual users read, but rather how well the page performs overall. This helps us to build a better service for you. 

## Cookies

We may place a text file called a "cookie" in the browser files of your computer. The cookie itself does not contain personal information although it will help us to relate your use of the site to information you have voluntarily provided to us. The only personal information that a cookie can contain is information that you supply yourself. A cookie cannot read data from your hard disk or cookie files created by other sites. Fitness Management uses these cookies to track user traffic patterns (as described above). 

You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you have set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each new cookie. You do not need to enable your browser to accept cookies to use this site. You will need to accept the cookies to view pages that require registration and to participate in the Forums. 

## Security

Fitness Management Publications operates secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall and password protection systems. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary and only authorized individuals have access to the information provided by our customers. 

## Your Consent

By using this site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Fitness Management. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post these changes on this page of our site so that you may remain informed and aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it to third parties.
